{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1174","name":"Palmer Park Preparatory Academy","address":"3901 Margareta","zipcode":"48221","owner":"Detroit Board of Education","licenseNumber":"035260","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Public School","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"210.0","coords":"-83.13879,42.42725","geojson":{"id":"1174","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.1387947549999,42.42725226]},"properties":{"name":"Palmer Park Preparatory Academy","owner":"Detroit Board of Education","address":"3901 Margareta","zipcode":"48221","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"035260","establishmentid":"1174","establishment_type":"Public School","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"210.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/30/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1656","name":"Boston Market #976","address":"18610 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1168","name":"Locker Room Lounge","address":"18290 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"5251","name":"Livernois Fresh Fish","address":"18280 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"2467","name":"China Wok","address":"18670 Livernois Ave ","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"51622673","name":"Biggby Coffee","address":"18685 Livernois","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"5301","name":"Mr. Fofo's Deli","address":"19166 Livernois","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"5208","name":"The Avenue \"An International Kitchen\"","address":"19163 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"51622833","name":"Legends Pizza on the Ave","address":"19163 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"5428","name":"BabyBack's Open Pit","address":"7108 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"51622453","name":"Narrow Way Cafe LLC","address":"19331 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"4617","name":"Kuzzo's Chicken & Waffles LLC","address":"19345 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"4903","name":"Babyback's Open Pit","address":"17310 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"3928","name":"1917 American Bistro","address":"19416 Livernois","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"5078","name":"Papa's Pizza - JNL Pizzaria, Inc.","address":"7410 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"331","name":"Gregg's Pizza BBQ","address":"17160 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"3986","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken #111","address":"17171 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1528","name":"Little Caesar's Pizza #167","address":"17200 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1547","name":"Gesu Elementary","address":"17139 Oak Dr","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"51622487","name":"Bucharest Grill","address":"19492 Livernois","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"51622638","name":"Jam Jomar XXV II (McDonalds)","address":"17121 Livernois #10902","zipcode":"48221"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44065","inspectionDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"41758","inspectionDate":"2018-03-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Adulterated/contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"4-301.12","violationDescription":"(A) Except as specified in ¶ (C) of this section, a sink with at least 3 compartments shall be provided for manually washing, rinsing, and SANITIZING EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS. (Pf)   \r\n(B) Sink compartments shall be large enough to accommodate immersion of the largest EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS. If EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS are too large for the WAREWASHING sink, a WAREWASHING machine or alternative EQUIPMENT as specified in ¶ (C) of this section shall be used. (Pf)\r\n(C) Before a 2-compartment sink is used the PERMIT HOLDER shall have its use APPROVED.\r\n(D) A 2-compartment sink may not be used for WAREWASHING operations where cleaning and SANITIZING solutions are used for a continuous or intermittent flow of KITCHENWARE or TABLEWARE in an ongoing WAREWASHING process.\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Three compartment sink","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Install to meet requirements"},{"violationCode":"3-202.15","violationDescription":"FOOD packages shall be in good condition and protect the integrity of the contents so that the FOOD is not exposed to ADULTERATION or potential contaminants. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food package(s)","subItem":"Cans","problemDescription":"Dented, dented on seam or swollen","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"restroom","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Cooler(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not covered","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep covered."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"40704","inspectionDate":"2017-11-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"39234","inspectionDate":"2017-07-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"37019","inspectionDate":"2016-11-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1174"}}